qandas.com 2012-10-10

# Privacy Policy - Featured Q&As

At QandAs.com, we are committed to protecting online user privacy. This "Privacy Policy" discloses the privacy practices governing our knowing collection, use, and disclosure of information. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below. 

Anonymous User Information: QandAs.com collects some anonymous information each time you visit QandAs.com so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with QandAs.com before we can collect this anonymous information. We do not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, e-mail address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. QandAs.com does not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or email address, in order for you to use the QandAs.com search. QandAs.com assigns an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited QandAs.com, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. We analyze this information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. QandAs.com may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of the QandAs.com search. 

 Third-Party Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect data when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>[ ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Cookies: We use a feature of Internet web browsers called a "cookie," which is a small file that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. This enables us to store user preferences and track user trends and search patterns. We use cookies to improve the quality of the QandAs.com services and to better understand how users interact with us. We do not and cannot use Cookies to retrieve individual personally identifiable information about you from your computer unless you knowingly and willingly provided such information. The cookie technology we use cannot obtain information from your hard drive or pass on a computer virus. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some QandAs.com features or services may not function properly without cookies. 

Information security: We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

Aggregated General Information: We may share aggregated general information about our site with our corporate partners or others. Examples of this include the number of users who searched for "Web Site Statistics", the daily number of unique visitors, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Aggregated data does not contain any personally identifiable information that could be used to contact or identify you. Information sharing We may share personally identifying information to other companies or individuals in any of the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. 
  * We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * When required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of QandAs.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent. 
  * We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the Canada or any other country in which QandAs.com or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country. 
  * QandAs.com may use third party service providers to serve ads and emails on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and emails and use information about your visits to QandAs.com so that we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third parties service providers anonymous information about your site navigation. 
  * We may share certain information about you with carefully selected business partners, including those who may offer services that complement those provided by us or which we believe may be of interest to you. We may also disclose information to third parties who assist us in providing our services to you. For example, we may engage third parties to make improvements on our site, to offer new products and to allow us to customize your experience on the Site. 

We utilize Google Advertising on some pages. * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. 

Correspondence: If you contact QandAs.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address. 

Third Party Information Gathering: QandAs.com includes content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy QandAs.com contains links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that QandAs.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Children's Privacy: QandAs.com does not knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age nor do we knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties. 

Sale of Assets: In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to the business of QandAs.com, we reserve the right to include any or all stored personal information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company. 

Changes to Privacy Policy: We reserve the right to amend or revise this privacy policy from time to time. We will post these changes to this page. Use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used.
